{
    "id": "87db64e48fa54a8991679dbe3b975c67",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Will you wait here ………………….. I come back?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I will visit you ………………… I have time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "when",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The train will have left …………………. the time we reach the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The train had left …………………. we reached the station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by",
                "before"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can leave ………………….. you are ready.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as soon as",
                "when",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to finish it …………………. you leave.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "before",
                "as soon as",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I hurt myself …………………. playing cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "whenever",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I injured my foot ……………….. I was playing cricket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "while",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He gave me the message …………………… I arrived.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "moment",
                "the moment",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will only pay you …………………. you finish the work on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}